该你走了  小姑娘
Your move, pumpkin.
我在思考
I'm thinking.
米奇  拿着
Mitch, grab that.
上去吧
Go on.
你不能一直思考
You can't think forever.
迟早得出手
Sooner or later, you've got to make a move.
反正你也从不让我赢
You never let me win anyway.
让了就不算赢了
Well, that wouldn't be winning.
我爸爸以前常这么说
That's what my daddy used to say.
他也经常下棋赢我
He used to beat me at chess, too.
他什么都比我好[双关]
Heck, he used to beat me at everything.
你认识这个人吗
You know this guy?
你爸爸刻薄吗
Was your dad mean?
有时候吧
Sometimes.
你坏吗
Were you bad?
有时候吧
Sometimes.
你一直在路上漂泊吗
So you've been on the road all this time?
对
Yeah.
你没事吧  布莱恩
You okay, Brian?
怎么了  小姑娘
What is it, pumpkin?
我坏吗
Am I bad?
什么
What?
你为什么会这样想
Why would you think that?
我爸爸总是对我很刻薄
My dad was always mean to me.
你很好
Hey, you're good.
真的
You are.
我们的营地离这里半英里
We've got a camp about a half a mile from here.
绝对不行  马丁内斯
Hell, no, Martinez.
我们那边人已经够多了
We got too many mouths as it is.
看在老天的份上  他们带着个小孩
They got a kid for Christ's sake.
如果你跟我们回去
Hey, if you do come back with us,
就得接受两件事
there's two things you got to accept.
第一  我掌权
One, I'm in charge.
第二  不许成为累赘
Two, no deadweight.
大家都得遵守
That goes for everyone.
要么做出贡献  要么就被赶走
Contribute or be cast out.
你能接受吗
Can you live with that,
布莱恩
Brian?
你我  你妈妈  还有塔拉姨妈
You, me, your mom, and Aunt Tara,
我们都会没事的
we're gonna be okay.
因为我们是好人吗
'Cause we're good?
我们都是吗
All of us?
该你了
Your turn.
布莱恩
Brian?
该你了
It's your turn.
我在思考
I'm thinking.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：冰蓝  33来了  Reginamoon  卫老哥  Eowyn  小饭  蘑菇
时间轴： 涛涛  加森  雪贵人 后期：  、青衣
校对： 卫老哥  米小勒  冰蓝  送小孩    监制： 送小孩
你今天出去吗
You going out there today?
去找补给品
Supply run.
马丁内斯和杜尔根兄弟
Martinez and the Dolgen brothers.
我要在营地建立一个护士站
I'm gonna set up a nurses' station for the camp.
他们有这个需要
They need one.
-抱歉  莉莉  这地方...  -别说了
- I'm sorry, Lily. This place is-- - Stop it.
我想为我们找到更好的地方
I wanted something better for us.
这个营地不错了
This camp is good.
我们会让这里变得更好
We'll make it better.
有鱼吗
How's the fishing?
没鱼了  池塘水质不好
There isn't any. Pond's dead.
这是一潭死水
As a doornail.
但我们还可以抓点兔子  臭鼬
We still got rabbits, skunks,
负鼠什么的来吃
some possum out here.
你还是管好你自己吧  独眼老布
You better watch your ass, One Eye Bri.
你确定我们走对方向了吗
You sure we're headed in the right direction?
照着霍华德的地图走的
If Howard's map is right.
真应该把他拖出来问个清楚
We should have dragged his ass out here to make sure.
人家老年人  哪里走得动
He's an old man. He can barely walk.
所以我才说拖着他走
That's why I said dragged.
希望这趟没白跑
Hope this is worth it.
也许他是那种末日生存主义者
Supposedly this guy was a survivalist type.
他的小屋里或许能找出有用的东西
His cabin might have stuff we can use.
说不定他还活着
Hell, maybe he's still alive.
我觉得危险
I won't keep my fingers crossed.
嘿  独眼龙  你在干嘛
Hey, One Eye. What you doing?
这是什么
The hell is this?
骗子
看来他把某人惹毛了
Somebody pissed somebody off.
管他呢
Who gives a shit?
死了一了百了
That guy's got nothing to worry about anymore.
继续走
Let's go.
-这个伤口很深  -没事
- It's a deep cut. - No, that's nothing, ma'am.
不过是玩刀子玩过头了  很快就好了
I just got cute with my knife, that's all. I'll be fine.
那么...
So...
我叫艾丽西娅
Alicia.
哦对  艾丽西娅
Alicia. Right.
你是海军陆战队的吗
You in the Marines or something?
我是陆军预备役
Army. In the reserves.
用的M4步枪对吧
An M4, huh?
你有意见吗
You don't approve?
别误会
I mean, don't get me wrong,
用M4步枪打近战不错
an M4 is great for close combat,
但作为野战武器的话
but as a field weapon?
尘土飞扬易卡壳  还是算了吧
With all that dirt and dust, no, thanks.
我不太喜欢长枪
I've never really been into big guns anyway.
我更喜欢史密斯威森手枪
I'm more of a Smith & Wesson gal.
方便又好用
Less fuss, you know?
你尽喜欢装逼对吧
You always this full of shit?
没错
Yes, I am
强奸犯
凶手
自杀了
Took himself out.
你觉得是他杀了那些军人吗
You think he's the one who 86'd those military guys?
-他的头还在  -没剩多少了
- He still has his head. - Some of it, anyway.
进屋看看
Let's see what he's got inside.
听到了吗  里面有行尸
You hear that? There's one in there.
肯定被卡住了出不来
Must be stuck if it ain't coming out.
要进去吗
We going in?
你吓尿了吗  磨蹭什么
You want us to wait till you finish pissing in your pants?
-不  我只是  -别废话了
- No, I'm... - Cut the chatter.
进去吧
Let's go.
-很近了  -安静
- It's close. - Quiet.
-它出来了  -闭嘴
- It's out. - Shut up.
赶走它
Get it off of me!
把它弄下来
Get it off of me! Get it off of me!
快把它弄下来
Get it off of me!
皮特
Pete!
假如当时坑里只有你一人
If it was just you in that pit,
我是不会把你带进营地的
I wouldn't have brought you into the camp.
要不是那些和你在一起的人
If it weren't for the people you were with...
那个小女孩儿...
the girl...
你感觉不太一样了
You seem different now.
变了
Changed.
是不是
Are you?
是的
I am.
那就好
Good.
这人有堆好东西
The guy had some good stuff.
罐头
Canned food.
我们有啤酒喝了
We got beer.
天呐  这儿发生什么了
Man, what happened here?
这间小屋里到底发生了什么
I mean, what the hell was going on in this cabin?
他养着那些行尸吗
Was he storing those biters?
她们是他的妻子和小孩
They were his wife and kid, man.
不  它们是行尸
No, they were biters.
那些头又是怎么回事
What about those heads?
那些头的主人惹错了对象
Belonged to the guys who did the wrong thing to the wrong man.
我们还是别细想这事了
Probably best not to think too much about it.
你最好听独眼老布的话  皮特
Better listen to One Eye Bri, Pete.
我永远也分不清他是在使眼色还是在眨眼
I can never tell if he's winking or blinking.
但你知道如何控制的  是吧  老布
But you know how to regulate, don't you, Bri?
他一直是这样吗  马丁内斯
He was always like this, Martinez?
是啊  喜怒不形于色
Oh, yeah. Ice in the veins.
你应该看看他当年风光的样子
You should have seen him back in the day.
你们大伙儿呢
What about you fellas, huh?
在这巨变发生前你是做什么的
What did you do before it all changed?
我是
I was...
我是个冰淇淋车司机
I was an ice cream truck driver.
之后我鸟枪换炮
Till I upgraded my life
成为了一个坦克驾驶员
and I became a tank operator
为美国陆军服务
for the US Army.
当一切变糟之后
Then when everything went tits up,
我离开了军队  开走了坦克
I got the hell out and took my ride with me.
假如你有一辆坦克的话
End of the world don't mean shit
世界末日就不算什么屁事了
when you got a tank.
我也是陆军
I was Army, too.
驻扎在本宁堡
Stationed out of Fort Benning.
灾难降临后我还在那待了一阵子
Stayed for a while after it all started.
这就是我家皮特
That's my Pete.
他太忠心了  不愿离开
He's too loyal to bounce.
你呢  布莱恩
What about you, Brian?
当时你在做什么
What did you do when it all went bad?
生存
I survived.
等等  你父亲是天主教神父
Wait, your father was a Catholic priest?
没错
That's right.
所以神父当了爹吗
So the father became a daddy?
的确给教堂带来了一些麻烦
It caused some problems with the Church a little bit.
这些故事布莱恩以前都听过
This is all stuff Brian's heard before.
我们在一起待过很长时间
We spent a lot of time out there together.
你们在这里做得很好  我是说这个营地
You've done all right here. I mean this camp.
这是一切发生之后我第一次有安全感
It's the first time I've felt safe since all this started.
我跟布莱恩之前待的地方挺不错
The place Brian and I lived before kind of worked.
我想让这里也一样
I guess I wanted that again.
听起来你们的旧营地非常好
Sounds like your old camp was pretty sweet.
你们有围墙  对吗
You guys had walls, right?
没错  那是
Yeah. Yeah, it was...
那是个好地方
it was a good place.
这里也是个好地方  对吗
This place is good, too, right?
你知道的
You know it.
希望有一天我能听听详情
I want to hear all about it someday.
布莱恩一个字都不肯说
Brian won't say a word.
过去的事就让它过去吧
I say leave the past in the past.
好吧  很久以来第一次
Well, for the first time in a long time,
-我醉成一坨屎了  -塔拉
- I'm shitfaced. - Tara.
抱歉  梅根  别说那个词  好吗
Sorry. Megan, don't say that, okay?
-你想走了吗  -好
- You want to get out of here? - Yeah.
谢谢款待  尤其谢谢你们的啤酒
Thanks for the dinner. Double thanks for the suds.
好  再见
Yeah. Boom. There you go.
-注意安全  -好
- Be safe. - Yep.
我想我也该走了
I think, um-- I think I'm gonna go.
你确定吗  我还有不少臭啤酒呢
You sure? I got a couple of skunky beers left.
我没事  谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
布莱恩  屋顶又漏了
Brian, the roof's leaking again.
你去修修吧  伙计
You should fix that, man.
我会的
I'll do that.
回见  小娃娃
Later, muneca.
差点忘了  有个惊喜给你
Almost forgot. Got a surprise for you.
我靠
Aw, damn it.
再给我递一个
Hand me another one.
你知道他死了  对吗
You know he's dead, right?
香珀特
Shumpert?
伍德伯里之后他就不一样了
He was never the same after Woodbury.
他变得不顾死活
Yeah. He got reckless.
行尸在那边咬掉了他一块肉
Biter took a piece of him right over there.
我发誓  他都没想要躲开
I swear, he didn't try to get out of the way.
我亲手杀了他
I put him down myself.
就在那边
Right over there.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
有些事情你永远无法回头
There's some things you just can't come back from.
它们变成了你的一部分
They become a part of who you are.
不管你是否能够接受
Either you live with them or you don't.
看起来你接受的挺好
Well, you seem to be living with them pretty well.
你也一样
So are you.
那家人真是让你变了
That family, they brought you back.
你很幸运  我不能
You're lucky. I couldn't--
我不能再那么做了  不能冒那个险
I couldn't do that again. Couldn't risk it.
想到可能失去她们  我就无法安眠
Couldn't sleep at night knowing I was gonna lose them.
我不会失去她们的
I'm not gonna lose them.
是啊
Yeah.
你不认为你能保护营地的安全吗
What, you don't think you can keep this place safe?
我会尽力
I'll try.
希望我们能尽量做好准备
Hopefully we'll be prepared for whatever comes.
现在你来了
Now you're here,
也许我们可以分享权力
maybe we can share the crown a little.
天呐
Oh, Jesus.
早知道我就学学高尔夫了
I should have taken some golf lessons before the-
我不想这么做
I don't wanna do it!
我不想  我不想
I don't want it! I don't want it!
听见了吗  我也不想  该死的
You hear me? I don't want it, damn it!
我不想这么做
I don't want it.
布莱恩  我们回来了
Brian, we're home!
梅根  他睡觉呢
Megan, he's sleeping.
布莱恩
Brian?
你在发抖
You're shaking.
怎么了
What is it?
做了个噩梦  没什么
I just had a bad dream, that's all.
什么样的噩梦
What was it?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
大家听着
Listen up!
今天早上  我们在坑里
We found what was left of Martinez
找到了马丁内斯的残骸
in a pit this morning.
貌似他当时在打高尔夫
Looks like he was hitting some golf balls,
他喝多了
he got drunk,
然后掉进了坑里
he fell in.
那现在怎么办
So now what?
我将接管营地
I'm taking leadership of the camp.
-不  不  -等一下  都等等
- No. No. - Hold on now. Hold on now!
我们应该投票才对
We should vote on who leads, right?
-是啊  -你没权利就这么接任
- Yeah. - You can't just take over.
-闭嘴  婊子  -你说什么
- Shut your mouth, you little bitch. - What?
冷静
Hey, calm down!
大家都冷静
Calm down, all of you.
我们现在
We need each other
更需要团结一致
now more than ever.
能熬过这一切的唯一办法
The only way we get through this, through any of this,
就是团结一致
is together.
现在的安排是暂时的
Now this is temporary.
未来几天内我们会想办法选举
We'll find some kind of way to do a vote in the next couple of days.
但现在  一切照旧
For now, it's business as usual.
行吗
Okay?
你们听见他说的了
You heard the man.
解散
Move!
拜托了
Please?
做好准备  我们去找补给
Gear up. We're going on a hunt.
定量配给  修护栏  药品储备
Rationing, fences, medical supplies.
有无数个问题而人们期望我给出答案
There are 100 questions and people are looking to me for answers.
当领袖是很难
Well, it's hard to lead.
是啊  我需要点协助
Yeah, I could use some help.
有多少人
How many?
10个
10.
可能不到
Maybe less.
但他们供给很足
They got a lot of supplies, though.
也许我们该把他们吸收进来
Maybe we should take 'em in.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我们的供给只是勉强够分
We barely got enough to go around as it is.
听着  皮特  我知道你不想伤害任何人
Look, Pete, I know you don't want to hurt nobody.
我也不想  但我们需要那些供给
Neither do I, but we need those supplies.
我们直接过去
Now let's just go over there
拿到需要的东西  就回家
and take what we need and go home.
不采取暴力
No rough stuff.
-你想抢劫他们  -何不呢
- You want to rob 'em? - Why not?
我们需要他们的补给
We need their stuff.
-他们有枪  但如果我们动作快点  -不
- They got guns, but if we roll up on 'em quick--  - No.
不行  我们自己也能找到供给
No, we can find our own supplies.
走吧
Come on.
太搞笑了
What a joke.
我们干得挺好的
We did all right.
是啊  几只该死的松鼠  几罐炼乳
Yeah, a couple of damn squirrels, some condensed milk.
你还要我怎么样  我在努力呢
What do you want from me? I'm trying here.
你去哪儿
Where you going?
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
这不是行尸干的
This wasn't biters.
是人干的
People did this.
肯定是刚发生的
Must have just happened.
我们本来可以拿到供给的
We would have had those supplies.
死了这么多人
You're worried about supplies?
你还在担心供给  米奇
These people are dead, Mitch.
你说的太对了  他们死了
You're damn right they're dead!
反正他们都是个死
That was gonna happen either way.
现在倒让别人抢走了咱们的供给
Now some other group's got our stuff.
米奇  米奇  不
Mitch. Mitch, no!
他可能还活着
He might have lived.
可能吧
Might have.
需要这个吗
Need this?
布莱恩  出什么事了
Brian, what's going on?
-马上收拾你的东西  -怎么啦
- Pack your things, now. - What's happening?
等等  宝贝
Hold on, baby.
拿上你的衣服  带点吃的  快点
Grab your clothes, pack some food. Come on.
妈妈
Mommy?
-布莱恩  住手  -去找塔拉
- Brian, stop. - Get Tara.
我们得走了  这里不再安全了
We need to leave. It isn't safe here anymore.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我们不能就这么走人
We can't just run off.
我是营地里唯一的护士
I'm the only nurse in camp.
塔拉跟艾丽西娅在一起
Tara's got Alicia.
那梅根怎么办
What about Megan?
听着  这里就要出大事了
Look, things are about to go very wrong here.
我以前遇到过  不能再让你和梅根遭罪
It's happened to me before. I can't put you and Megan through that.
不能再失去你们了
Can't lose you again.
那皮特怎么办
What about Pete?
你说过他是个好人
You said he was a good man.
-我错了  -但是...
- Well, I was wrong. - But...
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
你相信我吗  莉莉
Do you trust me, Lily?
那就快收拾东西
Then pack your things.
我们今晚就走
We're leaving tonight, okay?
快点
Come on.
妈妈
Mommy.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
-艾丽西娅  -你应该开慢点
- Alicia. - Maybe you should slow down.
不行  我不明白  我不懂
No, I don't understand this. I don't understand this.
不管去哪里我们都在一起  好吗
Hey, we're together, okay?
营地里什么都有  有食物有住所
We have everything back there. We have food, we have shelter.
-布莱恩  -天呐
- Brian. - Oh, my god.
待在车里
Just stay in the car.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
生存
Surviving.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
米奇的事情
About Mitch.
进来吧
Come in.
我就知道会这样
I knew this was coming.
我总是得帮他擦屁股
I've been getting him out of trouble my--
皮特呢
Where's Pete?
他死了
He's dead.
现在你也要把我干掉吗
You gonna kill me, too, now?
因为我杀了营地里那个老家伙吗
Huh? For the old guy at the camp?
抽烟吗
Smoke?
你对我哥哥做了什么
Why did you do my brother?
关于那个营地  你说的对
You were right about that camp.
我们应该抢走他们的补给
We should have taken their supplies.
我不在乎你杀了那个老头
I don't care that you killed the old man.
像你哥哥那种人  总是坚持做对的事情
Men like your brother, always doing the right thing,
甚至以自己人为代价
even at the cost of their own people.
抽根烟吧
Go on. Have a cigarette.
我戒了
I quit.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我还记得我抽的第一根烟
I remember the first smoke I ever had.
我和我哥挤在车库里
Me and my brother huddled in the garage
吸着我爸的好彩烟
puffing on one of my dad's lucky strikes.
他肯定是闻到了烟味  接着就冲了进来
He must have smelled the smoke, because he came barging in,
想揍我们
looking to beat up on us.
但是我哥哥挡在我前面
But my brother got between us.
说是他偷的
Said he stole them.
根本不是  是我偷的
Wasn't true. It was me.
但我哥哥就是那种人
But that was my brother.
英雄
Hero.
他因此被揍得鼻青脸肿  肋骨断了一根
He got two black eyes and a broken rib for that.
但我还是挨了打
And I got beat anyway.
拿一根吧
Take one.
现在我接管了
I'm running things now,
我会尽我所能保护这个营地
and I will do everything it takes to protect this camp.
如果你加入我  我保证
Now, if you join me, I promise you
你再也不用担心自己的行为
you will never have to worry about whether you were doing
是对还是错
the right thing or the wrong thing.
因为为了营地
Because we will do
我们会做任何事
the only thing.
我们怎么对营地的人说皮特的事
What are we gonna tell the camp about Pete?
就说他在寻找补给时
We'll tell them he died on a supply run
为救我们而死
saving our asses.
你觉得人们会相信吗
You think they're really gonna believe that?
人们相信自己想相信的事
People believe what they want to believe.
人人都爱英雄
Everybody loves a hero.
外围防护如何了
How's the perimeter coming?
快好了  我们用车围起了整个营地
It's good. We got cars ringing almost the entire camp.
再去找点东西
I think a few more runs,
就能建起一个缓冲带了
we should have ourselves a nice little buffer.
坑里呢
And the pits?
行尸不断来  我们不断烧
They keep coming, we keep burning them.
不知道是不是因为太热了
I don't know if it's the heat or what,
最近它们变得非常多
but there have been a hell of a lot more of them lately.
-弹药呢  -充足
- And the armory? - solid.
我收集了营地的所有子弹
I rounded up all the ammo in camp.
我们的子弹都堆满了
We're officially stocked in the bullet department.
但还是告诉你的队员
Still, tell your crews
以后外出搜索只准用弓箭
supply runs are arrow only from now on.
子弹这年头很珍贵
Gunshots are a luxury.
留着它们迟早用的上
Sooner or later we're gonna need 'em.
对  不只是对付行尸
That's right, and not just for the biters.
米奇  我  还有皮特
Mitch and I and Pete,
我们见识过外面的人有多危险
we saw what people can do out there.
如果碰到陌生人  就避开他们
You come across strangers, you just avoid them.
回来告诉我们你在哪里看到了他们
Come back here and tell us where you saw them, okay?
解散
Let's go.
也许我们能找到更好的地方
Maybe we can find a better place.
你知道  如果
You know, if...
我们愿意去争取的话
we're willing to fight for it.
我们不用去找更好的地方
We don't need to find a better place.
这里就是家
This is home.
你是鬼  塔拉姨妈
You're it, Aunt Tara.
什么  我不能当鬼  我在放哨
What? I can't be it. I'm on guard duty.
我是个负责任的成年人
I have to be a responsible adult.
-你是鬼  -快去追她
- You're it. - Go get her.
-这不公平  -快跑  梅根
- No fair! - Run, Megan.
你不必独自承担
You don't have to do this alone.
抓到你了
Caught you.
塔拉姨妈
Aunt Tara!
梅根
Megan!
塔拉姨妈  不
Aunt Tara! No!
-妈妈  -梅根
- Mommy! - Megan!
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.